The End
Too bad.
Looks like I win again.
Hoorah, hoorah, hoorah, hoorah, hoorah.
Hard at work, I see.
Hand over the keys to the cells.
Huh?
Who the hell are you?
Really?
Seems your manners are as
foul as your body odor.
What did you say?
You've got a lot of nerve, little lady.
I could say the same about you.
Let's fix that, shall we?
Now, kneel before me!
Negative...
HOME!
Negative!
I'm not even fit to be a
worm on a fishing hook.
I'm gonna crawl into one of these
prison cells just to hide my shame.
Thank you, boys.
All right, let's go.
Not very lively in here, is it?
Hey, stop that! Huh?
Call, get up!
I know you.
Wait a second, you're Koby the hero!
I'll unlock this door
for you, and in return,
you'll free Master Moria
from his cell deeper inside.
Moria?
Gecko Moria is being held here?
Wait, are you telling me you want me
to help a notorious criminal escape?
I am, yes.
Because if you don't, then
he'll surely be killed.
How can I set him free?
All of us are Sting Stingers!
All of us
are Stingers!
The end of the day, the end of the day.
I want to go to the same place.
But it's one thing that shines.
The legends are coming up with me.
I don't have to end my life.
I don't have fun.
Zubyaya.
The loudest of the word.
Is my heart.
That's all about.
If the word is sent.
Then, these people will forget.
I love you. We are with you.
We are in the world.
We are still keeping them.
Let the world start?
We got some big news!
Captain Covey has escaped!
Are you serious?
Oh, yeah!
If he's free, the Commodore can't
stop us from going after him.
We'll be set for life if
we can catch him ourselves.
Then what the hell are we waiting for?
All right, he's already got a
bounty, so we'll be good to go!
All we gotta do is take
a cent at Crosskill.
Hell yeah!
I bought odds on him with a win
ticket, and the payout's gonna be huge!
How much will we get if we kill him?
You might want to sit down for this one.
His bounty is five stars!
That means he's worth
five treasure chests!
Five hundred million berries!
Captains are usually only worth one star!
They must really want
this guy dead, huh? Yeah!
All right, men!
The hunt is on!
We're about to hit the jackpots!
I've got an itch on the
left side of my chest.
That's where the slaves
are held before the sale.
Are you kidding me?
They're escaping!
The slaves are running for it?
No!
That means we can hunt them down!
Oh boy!
Don't even think about it!
Keep your claws in check!
Bring him back, now!
And you better not kill Koby, or
I'll make sure you answer to teach!
Wait, did that rock? Just talk? No.
Pizzotto knows we're here.
We need to run!
We're not gonna make it.
Please, Koby.
You need to get out of
here while you still can.
Don't let us slow you down.
I promised that I'd help you escape.
And you will, by using me as bait.
Run as fast as you can, and no matter
what, don't let the pirates catch you. Go!
I'll see you all again soon!
Thank you, Captain Kobe!
You're a living saint!
Why don't you capture the
damn slaves yourself, Pizarro?
Because I don't want Teach
to come back and chew me out.
Whenever I move too much, I end up
breaking things, and it's a huge mess.
Why don't I stop him, huh?
Forget it, Bazooka.
What are you gonna do?
If I set the town on fire, they'll
have nowhere to run, right?
That would be a complete catastrophe!
Don't you dare!
Teach is gonna be Furious!
Uh, what's that?
Burn him, you say?
Absolutely no burning anyone, you hear me?
We just finished repairing Rocky Port.
All right, have it your way.
We'll let Wolf handle it.
Wait. Wolf?
That's the worst idea I've ever heard.
He'll crush the whole
town into kitty litter.
Over here!
Damn it, what am I supposed to do now?
I can't keep running away forever.
I'll be okay.
I just have to hold out until
the others can get out of here.
I'll figure out the rest after that.
Over here.
I'm so glad you're here
Kobe cuz I've got big
plans I'm gonna turn pirate
island into a full-flex
country one that flies the
flag of the world government
that'll make me a king of
the blackbeard kingtown
So what do you think?
I think your plan's as
ridiculous as you are.
You really think the
government would agree to that?
To a country made up of criminals?
Hey!
Don't you know it's rude to
stomp on someone's dream?
They might see it my way, now
I've got you as a bargaining chip!
The day the Navy negotiates with
terrorists will be the day justice dies!
And I won't be your bargaining chip.
I can't be.
I'm a member of S .W .O .R .D.
The hell is S .W .O .R .D.?
Never heard of it.
So that's how it is.
This will not end well.
Call off the trade, Teach.
It won't work. Huh?
Since this kid's from S .W .O .R .D., that
means he's a Marine, but not officially.
Sword members surrender their navy code.
They aren't like their comrades.
They're marines who have
submitted their resignations.
They can pick fights with the four
emperors without permission from above.
They can also disregard orders at
their discretion and move as they like.
And that's the issue.
The navy is absolved of all
responsibility for their actions.
They can cut them loose as they see fit.
Ain't that cute?
Most breeds just sit on their asses
waiting for Daddy's permission to fight us.
But you do what you like,
consequences be damned!
I get it now!
I like your style!
That said, I'm not gonna change my plan.
Cause you're a special case.
It doesn't matter if
you're with Zorn or not.
The public won't like it
if the Navy abandons you.
It's bad press to turn
your back on a hero, right?
Your life's in the people's hands.
Looks like the world government
will lose credibility either way.
I think he gets the
message. We're done here.
Lock him up.
And don't let him escape!
Get back here, Koby!
Here's the deal.
I'll unlock this door
for you, and in return,
you'll free Master Moria
from his cell deeper inside.
Guess this is what I deserve
for helping a pirate.
But necessity knows no law!
Huh?
The hell's that?
Three Marines just showed up at the port!
Huh? Marines? That can't be.
Hurry up!
They're strong! Be careful!
Did someone come to rescue me?
No, stop it, Kobe.
This is not the time for your selfishness.
What's wrong with me?
Who are they? They're monsters!
Looks like they're heading
straight to the center of town!
What do they want from us?
I don't know! Just shoot!
What?
They didn't even flinch!
End of the line, monster!
Whoa!
His head came off!
Woo-hoo!
You see that?
That's how it's done!
They're not so tough now!
That hurts.
He's a Lokiotype!
What the hell is wrong with him?
His body's like clay!
Where are you, Koby?
Hey, look over there.
I swear I just saw those
buildings move on their own.
Yeah, sure they did, pal.
How's quitting drinking going for ya?
Be good and do as I say.
Now march forward!
Is she whipping that building?
That's weird.
Come on!
Where's your stamina?
Is that really the best you can do?
You are so pathetic.
I kind of feel like I
shouldn't be watching this!
Hi boys.
Finish staring.
We are.
Wait?
That mark!
You pirates act like you've
never seen a marine before.
How adorable.
Come here.
Let me teach you a lesson.
What now?
I'm done for!
Eyes on the target, boys!
Ready, aim, fire!
Huh?
What? What?
What?
Oh my! How lovely!
Wait no!
What is this?
Where are these goddamn
flowers coming from?
Wait, I've seen this.
Of course!
Dr.
Vegapunk invented this!
In fact, it earned him
the Mobile Peace Prize!
Nobody cares about that, okay?
Who the hell picked this two our guns?
Hey, Kobe!
Come here and stay close to me!
But not in a weird way!
Wait, Heibati?
What are you doing here?
Are those... That's right.
They're flower rounds.
But they won't last.
We have to hurry!
We need to go before the enemy's
gunpowder stops turning into flowers!
Also, I, uh...
I don't want your food to get cold.
Because I...
I...
I packed you a lunch. Huh?
No, I miss Walk!
I mean, you misheard me!
Goalik!
Prince, what's the status?
We're in the clear.
Everything went off without a hitch.
Colby's doing fine.
Wait a sec!
This place doesn't look right?
Where are we?
Hey!
Everyone look!
That building just moved!
No way!
It's too late They moved the
buildings and trapped us here.
All right, whenever you're ready.
Aim for the dead center.
I just got confirmation from Prince.
Everyone is in position.
We're ready, Vice Admiral.
Everyone, hang on tight!
To hell we go! Whoa!
Ha-ha!
OK, hurry!
If you're ready, I am too.
Whoa, what the hell is that?
I'm not sticking around to find out.
Look up!
There's a baby ship in the sky!
It's flying straight for us!
But why? And how?
Whose ship is that?
Oh, looks like it's falling.
We gotta go! Run away!
No way!
I know that ship!
No, that can't be right!
I thought he retired!
The legendary hero!
He's coming!
It's Vice Admiral Couran!
Koby!
I came to get you, boy!
Come on!
We have to take cover! Whip's red!
Take the way out of here!
What?
You want a piece of me?
I'm not worth any of this.
You would risk starting
a war just to protect me?
Hey, morons!
Who do you think you kidnapped?
Do you know who the kid is?
Kobe's not just the future of the Navy!
That boy is my favorite student!
Policy!
IMPACT!
Kill me alone, Marcus!
My back! Damn, Garp!
He's insane!
Where'd you go? Your deck!
Hey, pirates!
Not so fast!
We've got plenty more
firepower where that came from!
Still a few buildings left.
I must be losing my touch.
Losing your touch?
Quit rubbing it in, you old bastard!
Vice Admiral Garp!
Hey, there he is!
You all right, Kobe?
I'm so happy!
I thought my body was gonna die!
And once again, Garp overdid it.
Such a naughty boy, isn't he?
I can't believe he said Kobe is
the future of the Navy. As if.
I'll put that kid in his place.
I know you're too spoiled to know better,
but that's not the sort of
thing you should say out loud
Pashigi even people who
are from sword are here.
Hmm.
What have you got there
a big ball and chain?
We had no choice
Something!
We can't!
He-body!
She's frozen solid!
What?!
Kuzan...
Why, Kuzan?
Why are you doing this?!
Hunt Freezybody right now!
Woo-hoo! Hell yeah! It's Apigi!
You guys are dead now!
Go, Koza!
Don't get me in trouble, kid.
Can't have you getting away.
How would that look to teach?
Two years ago,
there was a struggle
to determine who would
be the next fleet admiral
at Navy headquarters.
To that end, Admiral Aka 'inu
and Admiral Alkechi had a duel.
The fight went on for ten days
before a victor was decided.
Akainu stood triumphant.
Regardless, Alkeji refused to serve
under Akainu as Fleet Admiral,
and so he resigned.
What the hell?
Black man is here!
Come on, get out of
town while you're down!
Hey!
What is this? What happened here? Stop!
Someone tell me who did this!
Wait.
I know what this is.
I don't even gotta ask.
There's only one guy in the
world who could pull this off.
I thought so.
Aokiji.
What's the big idea?
Turning my crew into ice cubes.
Fix it.
Why don't you fix your attitude?
Wouldn't do that if I were you.
Your friends will shatter and die.
Come on now, you think
I started this fight?
You know what kind of company you keep.
Also, I'm sure you
heard the news about me.
I'm in a state of mourning.
You shouldn't test me.
So let's cool it with
the demands, shall we?
Who's ready for more bombs?
Damn, Freezer Fingers,
you sure can't drink!
You're not so bad yourself, shitbag.
Okay, before the battle,
what does Akainu say?
We climbed the ranks together.
Now we fight to the death.
I'm starting to feel a
hot lump in my throat.
That's what he said.
And you know what I told him?
No shit, asshole, you're made of magma.
Look what that bastard did.
Took off my whole damn leg So that's what
happens when two admirals
decide to throw down,
huh?
So'd you pay him back or what?
Rip off one of his arms, maybe?
Nah.
But he's got some scars to remember me by!
That reminds me, Commodore.
He might know the man with the burn scar.
The what?
Who the hell's that?
The deal is, if we want
to make it to Laugh Tale,
we gotta find the Four Road Poneglyphs.
You know them when you see
them, cause they're bright red.
Kaido and Big Mom have one each.
But what about the other two?
They're still a mystery.
We're just hoping fate will
guide us to them. That's right.
Well, we do have one tiny lead.
We heard some man with the
Burnscar has one of them.
You mean me? No, not you!
You just got that the other day!
What the mystery, no.
Rumor has it that the man with the
burn scar sails on a pitch black ship.
But if anyone approaches it,
their ship will be whisked away,
swallowed up by a giant whirlpool.
I'd assume the fellow
has a Devil Fruit power.
Just a hunch, but I bet the
guy is with the government.
They've got their hands in everything
and plenty of dark secrets.
They know everyone needs those stones.
If they had one, all they'd have to
do is hold on to it, and we'd be sunk.
No pirate could find their way
to Laugh Tale or the One Piece.
The Poneglyphs, huh?
Brings back memories.
Hate to break it to you,
but I never saw a giant
red stone in Ohara.
I'd remember.
I haven't forgotten a thing
About that day the day I
watched my best friend rebel
against the government and
the day that I Saw those sad
eyes when I held that poor
lonely girl's fate in my
hands that story sounds boring
Commodore what should we do a power
like his could be quite useful
I say we take it while his Guards down
come
on then
you want to know
what it feels like to freeze the
Death take it easy buddy so the
rumors are true you're hunting people with
strong Devil Fruit powers, aren't you?
Then try to take mine, I dare you!
Whoa, whoa!
Listen to me!
My crew members are getting
carried away, that's all.
Let me apologize on their behalf.
I don't want to steal your power.
I want you to join my crew.
Are you nuts, an ex-Marine?
Why not?
You're out of a job now, right?
You got any place to go?
Anything you're planning to do?
Not going to be defending justice anymore.
Guess I've sunk pretty low, huh?
A good-for-nothing pirate's worried
about the state of my employment.
Men like us will find
trouble anywhere we go.
Can't run, so you might
as well face it head on.
What flag will you fly?
When you put your life on the line,
what will you be fighting for?
Tell me!
I've got my own brand
of justice my own code
this won't be nothing like
the navy i promise you.
Yeah i'm sure but i'll still
get stabbed straight in the back
you think sharing a couple of
drinks means i can trust you?
Of course not i don't think you
understand how pirates work.
We're not here to make friends we're
a crew but we're not buddy buddy.
We all have a common goal.
All pirates need is an
alignment of interests.
You're free now, Kuzan.
Your choice.
What do you really want?
Stop this, Kuzan!
Fahibari out right now!
Let Kobe escape from here!
Come back to the Navy!
You never change, huh?
Can't stop to think you'd
just run your mouth.
But I'm afraid I can't
help you today, Garp.
I'm sorry.
You've always been straightforward.
I admire that.
You inspired me.
So I'm living the way I want to now.
You damn fool.
Ice-Ball!
Vice Admiral Garp!
Vice Admiral!
Your old student and your new student.
Would you do anything to save
Kobe, even if it kills me?
What are you doing bringing up the past?
I taught you to live
in a moment, didn't I?
How the hell did he break free?
Here's another lesson.
Men who waver are weak!
Come on, Blue Holes!
Meanwhile, on the coast
of Winner Island...
Ugh.
He-he-he-he-he.
Now that your ship is
out of the picture you
haven't just lost your
right to call yourself.
A pirate you lost your
only escape you stole 100
hearts that day at Rocky
Port you had to expect
some kind of payback from
me those poor pirates
back at my base living
every damn day in fear.
So I think I'll bring it
back to your heart as a gift.
Bet that'll have the sad
bastard Chop it for joy.
Oh wow, you made this for me?
But I haven't been able to test it,
so I can't guarantee it'll work.
Let me think.
We could sell your fruit, but I
think I could put it to better use.
They say it can grant
someone eternal life, right?
Shoot!
Stay away!
Huh?
That's my captain!
It can't be so long, but how?
The moon isn't even out!
Ah!
Captain!
Damn it!
They're headed to the sea!
Get them now!
Take me back, Beppo.
They're my friends.
I can't leave them.
I'm sorry, Captain!
We can't risk it.
But your crew was forged in
the cold waters of the North.
Have faith in them through every fight.
They've held strong.
They won't die here.
We've overcome so much together.
We have to survive.
All of us!
Don't die, Captain!
We need you!
The Bartlett-Winner Island in
the New World came to an end.
Blackbeard destroyed the Polar Tang,
the submarine of the Heart
Pirates, and it sank into the sea.
The Heart Pirates, led by
Trafalgar Law, were defeated.
Do you know how to run
away from the world?
I don't know how to run away,
but I don't know how to run away.
I'm still looking at my head in my head,
I'm still looking for the future.
I'm laughing at you.
I'm singing the same song.
If you're a big man,
I don't want to forget.
I'm waiting for you to come to the end.